

## IQRA KALIM

GRADUATED 23–BS SOCIAL SCIENCES AT SZABIST UNIVERSITY KARACHI. CGPA: 3.5

#### **ABOUT ME:**

I've recently graduated in BS Social Sciences program at SZABIST University Karachi, with majors in International Relations. I'm a creative, motivated and responsive individual that has a drive to accomplish every task that I'm entrusted with as I am committed to multi-tasking and meeting my deadlines. As a Social Sciences student and as an individual I aim to interact with a work environment that challenges me and provides me with insightful exposure for my future growth, I'm keen on learning various skills from diverse individuals.

**My Ultimate Goal:** To adapt to new experiences and replenish my self with a sense of self-actualization.

CONTACT

PHONE: 03142344488

EMAIL:

igka308@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION**

SZABIST 2019- 2023

Bachelor of Social Sciences (BSSS)

D.A PUBLIC SCHOOL O & A LEVELS 2016-2018

College for my A'Levels (Humanities group)

THE HAMPTON SCHOOL (CLIFTON BLOCK 6) 2009-2015

O'Levels (Commerce group)

## **EXPERIENCE**

INTERNSHIP AT INITIATOR HUMAN DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION 2021-2022

**Assistant Director of HR in Literary Society 2020-2021** 

At SZABIST (Shaheed Zulfikar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology)

#### PARTICIPATORY REPRESENTATIVE OF BOOK CLUB IN 2017

At my College (D.A Public School O & A Levels)

#### **CERTIFICATE AND ACHIEVEMENTS:**

I got my first ever Research Paper published on **ResearchGate** in 2021: <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Igra-Kalim?ev=hdr\_xprf">https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Igra-Kalim?ev=hdr\_xprf</a>

I did a 6 day Basic Graphic Designing Course from **Creativo** on Photoshop CC and Adobe Illustrator during Covid-19 in 2021. Received a certificate of appreciation for it.

## SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Teamwork Skills
- Interpersonal Skills
- Communication
- Analytical Skills in comprehensive written documentations
- MS (Word & PPT)
- Problem-Solving

# **Languages Fluently Spoken: English** ✓ Urdu ✓ Sindhi **HOBBIES**: Reading Articles Crafts and Arts Writing poetry Watching Documentaries and reshaping my views. > Currently at Present: Enrolled in "Government Initiative for Artificial Intelligence & Computing" in Quarter-2 learning Web Development (Front End Development: Html, Custom & Tailwind Css paired with Next.Js)